Oh.
يا إلهي
Brother, why are you in such a hurry?
لماذا أنت مستعجل؟
All right. All right.
حسناً، حسناً
Humph.
هاه
Ah.
آه
Oh.
يا إلهي
Brother, why did you fall down?
أخي لماذا سقطت؟
Hurry up.
بسرعة بسرعة
Ouch!
يا إلهي
Ouch! Ouch!
لا تغضب لا تغضب
It's fake?
مزيف
It's fake.
مزيف مزيف
It's all fake.
كلها مزيفة
Well.
ماذا؟
Brother.
أخي الكبير
So you are a toy boy.
أنت شاب
No.
لا
What else is true about you?
ما هي الحقيقة؟
I won't talk to you anymore.
لن أهتم بك مرة أخرى
Don't go.
لا تذهبي
Hey.
مهلاً.
I won't dislike you.
لن يكرهك
A toy boy is good too.
إنه جيد أيضًا
A toy boy is quite popular.
إنه لطيف
Hey.
مهلاً
Well.
يا إلهي
Our master said
هل قالت صاحبة القصر
young people would have cars and beauties.
لا يمكن أن ينقص الشباب الجميلات
Here you are.
أحضرتها لك
Mr. Jiang.
سيد جيانغ
I'm here to serve you.
أنا هنا لخدمتك
No, I...
لا لا أنا أنا
A talented man
هل أنت موهوب؟
should match a beauty.
مناسبة للمرأة الجميلة
This is really...
هذا حقا
It's shameful.
هذا محرج
A gentleman should stay out of danger.
الرجل النبيل لا يقف تحت الجدار الخطير
Now you're found in a suspicious position.
‫مثل هذا
I'd better avoid it.
من الأفضل أن أتجنب
Bah!
أف
Don't be shy.
لا تخجل يا سيدي
Master asked me to come here.
طلبت مني الصاحبة أن آتي
He said you...
قلت إنك
No, I didn't.
لم أفعل
Don't talk nonsense.
لا تتفوه بالهراء
You still don't admit it?
أنت لا تعترف
You just did this to me...
لقد قلت للتو
One, two, three.
واحد
I did this
أنا معك
because we were practicing dancing.
‫لأننا نتعلم من مهارات الرقص يا أخي‬
I wasn't interested in you.
أنا لا أحبك
You're bad.
أنت شرير
Go, go, go. Hurry up.
هيا بنا
Let's dance together another day.
لنرقص معا في يوم آخر
Yo.
أوه
One, two, three.
هذا واحد
Show more steps for me.
أعطني واحدة أخرى
Come on.
هيا
One, two, three, four.
واحد اثنان ثلاثة أربعة
No, I...
لا أنا
Uncle Hao misunderstood me.
العم هاو أساء فهمي
He misunderstood you?
لقد أساء فهمك
What?
ماذا؟
I think he knows you well.
أعتقد أنه يعرفك جيدًا
You're perfect.
.أبذل قصارى جهده
Hey, Xingxing.
يا النجوم
You wronged me.
لقد ظلمتني
I wronged you?
لقد ظلمتك
Now you're acting weird
الآن بمجرد أن نتحدث عن الرجل المشوي
when it comes to Fork Man.
أنت غريب الأطوار
You're still brazen.
والآن أنت صريح
You have double standards.
أشعل الشعب الفانوس
No.
لا
Speaking of Fork Man,
بالحديث عن الرجل المشوي
I have something to say.
لدي ما أقوله
Just say it.
نعم
Since Fork Man appeared,
منذ ظهوره
you've become more and more unscrupulous.
أصبحت أكثر شجاعة
You provoked me in front of me.
أشعل النار أمامي
Yes.
نعم
Wasn't this good?
أليس هذا جيدًا؟
I provoked you and you didn't follow me.
أشعل النار وأنت أشعل المصباح
Let's play our own games.
لنلعب
You...
أنت
Shame on you.
هذا محرج
No.
لا
I won't follow you.
أشعل المصباح
I'll still do that.
أشعله للعب
Brother.
يا أخي
Don't cry.
لا تبكي
Don't feel inferior.
لا تشعر بالذنب
Even if you don't have any beard
حتى لو لم تنمو لحيتك
or leg hair,
لا يوجد شعر رجلك
I won't dislike you.
لن يكرهك الأخ الأكبر
You're so annoying.
أنت مزعج جدا
Just leave me alone.
دعني أبقى وحدي لبعض الوقت
Can you leave me alone?
هل يمكنك تجاهلي؟
How can I leave you alone?
كيف يمكنني تجاهلك؟
I won't give up on you.
لن يتخلى عنك
Ah.
يا إلهي
You're so annoying.
أنت مزعج
All right. All right.
حسنًا حسنًا حسنًا
Don't be angry.
لا تغضبي
I can't say anything positive.
أخي الكبير لا يستطيع التحدث
But I really treat you as my own brother.
لكن الأخ الكبير يعاملك كأخي
Then why did you make me angry?
ما زلت غاضبًا مني؟
Alright. Don't be angry.
حسنًا، لا تغضب، لا تغضب
Come on, smile for me.
‫هيا ابتسم الأخ الأكبر‬
I'm a pro at taking care of a cripple.
‫الأخ الكبير يعتني بالعرج محترف‬
Put me down.
أنزلني
You're double-faced.
يا لك من أحمق
I know it clearly.
أنت واضح
I don't need your care.
لا أريدك أن تعتني بي
Hey.
مهلاً
What?
ماذا؟
Look.
انظر
Wow.
‫واو‬
So many stars.
الكثير من النجوم
Stars only look pretty
النجوم جميلة فقط هكذا
I get drunk and forget that the stars in the water are just reflections.
♫ عندما ثملت لا أعرف السماء في الماء ♫
I fall asleep on the boat, and I lie down on the Milky Way in my dream.
♫ كل السفينة مليئة بالحلم ♫
What does it mean?
ماذا تعني؟
It means I like the scene very much.
يعني أنها جميلة جدًا يعجبها كثيرًا
I'm a rough man.
أنا شخص قاس
I don't understand what you scholars say.
لا أفهم ما يقوله المثقفون
All I know is that the scene pretty.
أعرف فقط أنها جميلة
If you like it, say you like it.
إذا أحببتها فقل أحبها
Is the scene pretty?
هل أبدو جميلة؟
Yes.
أجل
Do you like it?
هل أعجبك؟
I get drunk and forget that the stars in the water are just reflections.
♫ عندما ثملت لا أعرف السماء في الماء ♫
I fall asleep on the boat.
♫ كل السفينة تحلم ♫
I lie down on the Milky Way in my dream.
‏(تهديد النجوم)‏
Today,
اليوم
you and I
نحن الإخوة
are lying in the deep woods,
نستلقي في الغابة
looking at the stars.
ونشاهد النجوم
What the beautiful scenery.
ومناظر جميلة
One word.
كلمة واحدة
Beautiful.
جميل
Two words.
كلمتين
Very enjoyable.
ممتع جدا
Three words.
ثلاثة كلمات
Okay.
جيد
This is great.
هذا رائع
Look, there are green stars.
انظر، هناك نجوم خضراء.
I see it too.
لقد رأيت أيضاً
Why do I feel
لماذا أشعر
they're getting closer to us?
يقترب منا أكثر فأكثر
They're wolves.
إنه ذئب
Brother Bu Ying.
الأخ الفائز
Brother, don't be afraid.
لا تخف يا أخي
It's morning.
‫إنه مشمس‬
Wait.
انتظر
Brother Mu.
أخي مو
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Xingchen.
النجوم
After we parted in the forest last time,
آخر مرة ودعنا في الغابة
we still have a lot to talk about.
هناك الكثير من الأشياء لم نتحدث عنها
Oh, but...
لكن لكن
It's late.
لقد تأخر الوقت
It's about Fork Man.
إنه يتعلق بشارك
Fork Man?
‫شاشاي‬
That's right.
صحيح
What's wrong with him?
ما خطب الرجل المشوي؟
Aren't you curious about the things
ألا تشعر بالفضول
happened in the martial arts world
ماذا حدث
I've been traveling in all these years?
في عالم الكونغ فو
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Get out.
اخرج
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Why is Mu Binghe in your room?
لماذا مو بينغ خه في غرفتك؟
He knocked on the door.
لقد طرق الباب
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
How did he follow you?
‫كيف تتبعني‬
You two still keep in touch?
هل ما زلتما على اتصال سري؟
Why are you so mean?
لماذا تتحدثين بهذه القسوة؟
Women are liars.
كلام المرأة كاذب
I knew it.
كنت أعرف
It's necessary to protect yourself
هذا الوقاية من الحريق والسرقة
You are unreasonable.
أنت غير معقول
You were angry because of Fork Man before.
من قبل بسبب الرجل المشوي
And now you're angry because of Brother Mu.
والآن بسبب مو
Why are you so narrow-minded?
لماذا أنت بخيل؟
How could you be so petty?
‫هذا كل شيء
I'm narrow-minded？
أنا بخيل
You two are alone in the same room.
أنتما في غرفة واحدة
I don't want to talk to you.
لا أريد التحدث معك
Hello?
ألو
Leave.
سأذهب
Get away.
اغرب عن وجهي
Let's eat.
كلوا الطعام
Fifth Master.
لاو وو
Hey.
مهلاً
Can you understand the relationships
هل تفهم العلاقة بين هؤلاء الثلاثة؟
I can understand.
هل تفهم؟
A situation of tripartite confrontation.
ثلاثة أرجل مستقيمة
It's the steadiest structure.
هل هو الأكثر ثابتة؟
Sister.
يا أختي الصغيرة
Am I right?
أليس كذلك؟
Alas.
حسناً
Jiang Buting. It's enough.
جيانغ بو تينغ، يكفي
We are in the same room.
الجميع في نفس الغرفة
Who are you sighing for?
‏إلى من تسمع؟‏
I'll leave then.
سأذهب
Stop!
توقف
Come back.
عد
Don't you have anything to say to me?
ألا لديك شيء لتقوله لي؟
No.
لا
Really?
حقا لا
I do.
لدي
I have something to tell you.
لدي شيء لأخبرك به
I'm sorry.
هل أنا آسف؟
Don't be angry.
لا تغضبي
I didn't mean it.
لم أقصد ذلك
And you also...
وأنت أيضًا، حسنًا
What?
ماذا؟
I-It's so fast.
بهذه السرعة
I've prepared for a long time.
لقد أعددت لفترة طويلة
I didn't do my best.
لم أبذل قصارى جهدي
But
لكن
Ting Ting is the best.
شياو دينغ دينغ هي الأفضل
He has the best temper, right?
مزاجها أفضل، أليس كذلك؟
He's also the cutest.
وألطف
Don't smile and grimace.
لا تبتسم لي
Okay.
حسنا
Although I forgive you,
على الرغم من أنني سامحتك
let me make it clear first.
لكن يجب أن أقول لك أولاً
Okay, go ahead.
حسنا حسنا تكلم
I know
أعلم
you grew up with Brother Mu.
لقد كبرت مع أخيك مو
Yes.
أجل
You two are childhood friends.
صداقتنا منذ الطفولة
But you should remember
لكن تذكري
that you have me now.
أنت معي الآن
Yes.
نعم
You insisted on forcing me.
أنت من أصر على كسر البطيخ
So you need to keep a distance from him.
لذا يجب أن تبقي مسافة معه
Yes, keep a distance.
نعم، حافظ على المسافة
Go on.
استمر
Actually, I don't have any requirements.
في الواقع ليس لدي أي متطلبات
I just want you to remember...
أريدك أن تتذكر
Yes.
نعم
You are mine.
أنت لي
No matter who your admirers are,
بغض النظر عن حبيب معجبين وأخي وأخي
they are not as important as me.
هم ليسوا مهمين مثلي
Who are they?
من هم؟
I don't know them at all.
لا أعرفهم على الإطلاق
Am I right?
أليس كذلك
Only you.
أنت فقط
But seriously,
لكن بجدية
I've already
لقد أخبرت مو
talked to Mu Binghe.
مع مو بينغ خه
I've made it clear to him.
سأوضح الأمر له
And he understood.
لقد فهم
So he came here to fulfill the dream
لذلك جئت هذه المرة
he had when he was a kid.
كان حلمًا في طفولته
He wanted to go into the martial arts world
يريد أن يسافر معي في عالم الكونغ فو
Really?
حقا
As long as you're not angry.
لا تغضب
Brother.
أخي
There seems to be a temple ahead.
يبدو أن هناك معبد أمامنا
Let's take a look.
لنذهب ونلقي نظرة
Brother, it's the God of Matchmaking Temple.
يا أخي إنه معبد وسيط الزواج في السماء
Let's go and pray.
لنذهب لزيارة
Two men don't need to pray to God of Matchmaking.
لا داعي للذهاب إلى معبد وسيط الزواج في السماء
We should worship Guan Yu, Saint of War.
يجب أن نعبد السيد قوان إر يه
Brother, we worship God of Matchmaking for marriage.
أيها الأخ الأكبر، معبد وسيط الزواج في السماء يطلب الزواج
Don't you want a gentle and virtuous sister-in-law?
ألا تريد زوجة لطيفة
I already have you. I don't need any sister-in-law.
أنا أملك أنت، ماذا تريد زوجة أخي؟
I still want to go.
ما زلت أريد الذهاب إلى اللقاء
Hey.
مهلاً
Well. Let's worship.
‫خلاص مع السلامة
I, Mu Yaoguang,
الثقة مو ياو قوانغ
pray to God of Matchmaking for a good marriage.
أتمنى أن يتزوج وسيط الزواج في السماء
I hope Yaoguang's future husband
أتمنى أن يكون زوج ياو قوانغ
is a gentle and considerate person.
‫هو زوج لطيف ومراعي
Are you hungry?
هل أنت جائع؟
A little.
قليلا
Look.
‫انظر
I hope Yaoguang's future husband can be strong.
‫أتمنى أن يكون زوج ياو قوانغ قويا
Put me down!
‫أنزلني
You're double-faced.
‫يا لك من غبي
I hope my future husband can love me.
آمل أن يكون زوجك في المستقبل ياو قوانغ يحب ياو قوانغ
God of Matchmaking.
وسيط الزواج في السماء
I'm not being unfaithful,
أنا لست صادقة
but...
بل
God of Matchmaking. God of Matchmaking.
وسيط الزواج في السماء وسيط الزواج في السماء
You don’t need to help me.
لا داعي أن تساعدني في ربط الخيط
I'm satisfied
لدي أخ مثله بجانبي
to have this man beside me.
أنا راضية
Don't ask others to bother me.
لا تدع الآخرين يزعجني
It rained nonstop
تمطر في منتصف الليل
Let's have a chat
في منتصف الليل
We'll look at each other.
حاجبان وفمك
I won't fall asleep if I hold my sister.
‫أمسك أختي ولم تنم‬
B-Brother.
أخي الكبير
Fourth Master, tell me.
أخي الرابع قل
We have a guest.
جاء الضيوف
She said...
قال
She said she was Miss Huo's good friend.
قال إنه الحديد للسيدة "هيو"
Yaoguang.
‫ياو قوانغ
It must be Yaoguang.
‫لا بد أنهم ياو قوانغ
What took you guys so long
‫لا أنتم تسيرون طريق الجبل
on the way up here?
لماذا أنتم متضايقون هكذا
Did something happen?
هل حدث شيء غير متوقع
What's that look on his face?
ما تعبيره؟
My brother.
أخي
Alright.
حسنًا حسنًا
-Brother. -Let's go. Don't be afraid.
أخي لنذهب لا تخف لا تخف
Aren't you worried at all?
ألا تقلق على الإطلاق؟
All right.
حسنًا حسنًا
Don't be angry.
لا تغضبي
Why should I be worried?
لا تقلقي
You're not pretty anymore.
لست جميلة
Turn around.
هيا، استدر
Oh.
يا إلهي
Not bad.
جيد جيد
Don't worry.
لا تقلق
Go practice your swordplay.
لنتدرب على سيفك
Your hair is longer.
شعرك طويل مرة أخرى
You don't worry, but I do.
لا تقلق أنا قلق
Am I fat?
هل أنا سمينة؟
No.
لا
Brother, let's go practice swordplay.
هيا بنا، لنتدرب
I have something to say to Xingchen.
لدي ما أقوله مع النجوم
Exactly.
أجل
Xingchen. Xingchen.
النجوم النجوم
No.
لا
Why are they so close?
لماذا هما مقربان جدا
It's not okay.
هذا لا يمكن
He...
هو
It seems that
يبدو
he doesn't know
الأخ الأكبر هو فتاة
his brother is a girl.
ألا يعرف أخي؟
You...
أنت
How did you know?
كيف عرفت
Because she used to wear a beard,
كانت تلصق لحية كبيرة من قبل
it's normal that I didn't recognize her.
من الطبيعي ألا أعرفها
Look at her now.
الآن هكذا
She is obviously a girl.
من الواضح أنها فتاة
You can get it.
هل لاحظت ذلك؟
Why can't your brother get it?
لماذا لا يستطيع أخوك أن يعرف ذلك؟
Maybe my brother only cares about swords.
ربما أخي يهتم بالسيف فقط
Do you think we should tell your brother
‫هل يجب أن نخبر أخاك
that Yaoguang is a girl?
‫أن ياو قوانغ فتاة
She'll tell him herself
‫إذا أراد ياو قوانغ أن يقول
if she wants to.
‫ستقول بنفسها
If she doesn't say anything, stay the same.
إذا لم تخبرها فلتبقى كما كانت
Okay.
نعم
You're right.
صحيح
Come on, baby.
تعالي يا عزيزتي
Miss.
عزيزتي
I'm coming.
أنا هنا
Xingchen.
النجوم
I miss you so much.
اشتقت إليك كثيرا
I miss you too.
أنا أيضاً أشتاق إليك
We haven't seen each other for a few days.
في الواقع لم نلتقي لبضعة أيام
But it feels like it's been a long time.
لكن أشعر أنني لم أرك منذ وقت طويل
Yes.
نعم
One day apart is like three years.
لم نلتقي يومًا واحدًا مثل ثلاثة أعوام
We haven't seen each other for days.
لم نلتقي منذ عدة أيام
It's like a lot of three years passed.
كم مر من الخريف؟
Hey.
مهلاً
I didn't tell you in detail during the day.
لم أخبرك بالتفصيل في النهار
What happened to you on the mountain？
ماذا حدث لكما في الجبل؟
What took you so long?
لماذا تأخرتم كثيرا
It was all because of Jiang Buying.
جيانغ بو فاز
Don't mention it.
لا تذكر ذلك
He was so annoying.
إنه مزعج للغاية
Oh.
أوه
Come on.
يا إلهي
Alright, I understand you.
حسنا فهمت
Although it looks like Bunting and I
على الرغم من أن بودينغ كان بخير معي اليوم
we just had a quarrel a few days ago.
لقد تشاجرنا قبل بضعة أيام
I managed to coax him.
لم يكن من السهل إقناعه
How?
كيف أغضبته؟
I just shook his arms
أنا أرقص هكذا
and he was not angry anymore.
سيكون بخير
How could it be so fast?
لماذا بهذه السرعة؟
Oh.
أوه
Just shake his arms.
يمكنك أن تهز
Why are you laughing?
لماذا تضحك؟
Have you ever heard a saying?
ألم تسمع جملة من قبل
"Love begets worry,
‫يسمى بسبب الحب
and worry begets fear."
بسبب الحزن
He was too afraid to lose you.
إنه خائف جداً من فقدك
When you were angry, he was afraid
لذلك عندما تغضب
that if he didn't follow your words,
كان يخشى أنه لن يتبع سلطتك له
you would ignore him.
لذا تجاهلته
You really know a lot, don't you?
أنت تعرف الكثير
Of course! I've read all the scripts
بالطبع
in the martial arts world.
لقد قرأت رواية الفنون القتالية بأكملها
There's nothing I don't understand.
كيف لا أعرف؟
Oh, I see.
نعم
So, what's the deal between you and Buying?
ما هي الحيلة التي تخططين فيها؟
He and I...
أنا وهو
We are...
نحن
What?
من أنتما؟
Huo Xingchen!
"هيو شينغ تشين"
Yes.
أجل
You're teasing me,
أنت تمزح معي
despite me helping you out！
لقد ساعدتك على الإجابة
Well.
‫خلاص
I've prepared some ordinary items
أعددت بعض
from Xiaoyao Palace for you all.
من قصر شياو ياو
Nothing special.
لا شيء مميز
It's hardly presentable.
لا أستطيع فعل ذلك
Enjoy them on your journey.
فلتستمتعوا في الطريق
Thank you, uncle.
شكراً يا عمي
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة
Uncle.
يا عمي
Second Master.
يا صاحبة القصر الثاني
It's time for us to leave.
سنغادر أولا
OK.
في الوسط
See you again.
أراك لاحقا
Third Master.
يا صاحبة القصر الثالث
See you.
هنا
Fourth Master.
صاحبة القصر الرابع
Take care.
اعتني بنفسك
OK.
حسنا
Fifth Master.
صاحبة القصر الخامس
Bye.
مع السلامة
Sixth Master.
يا صاحبة القصر السادس
I’m leaving.
سأغادر
Seventh Master.
صاحبة القصر السابع
Take care of yourself.
اعتني بنفسك
Sure!
جميل جدا
Take care!
اعتن بنفسك
Let's go.
لنذهب
Goodbye.
جميل جدا
Oh.
يا إلهي
The curtain has fallen.
تسقط الستائر
Zhi Dong, don't slack off.
أيها الأخ الثاني لا تتكاسل
Stick it back up.
ضعيها
The curtain falling down
إذا سقطت هكذا
affects the entire ambiance.
سيؤثر على النمط كله
The gold itself
هل هذا الذهب
is naturally beautiful
‫هكذا في الأصل‬
when exposed.
‫هل تظهرين؟ جميلة جدا‬
It's too vulgar to show gold.
‫أظهر الذهب مبتذل للغاية‬
It's not elegant at all.
ليست أنيقة على الإطلاق
Hurry up and fix it.
اذهبي بسرعة
Got it.
!กลาง
Brother
أخي الكبير
Come and open the gift from Uncle Yuwen.
تعال بسرعة لتفكيك الهدية التي أعطاها العم يو وين
Is it food?
هل هو طعام
I don't know.
لا أعرف
Not presentable?
لا أستطيع
Nothing spacial?
لا يوجد ميزة
ordinary items?
لا شيء مميز
Xingchen, look!
النجوم، انظروا
It's not surprising at all.
لا مفاجأة على الإطلاق
Hurry up. Put it away.
بسرعة بسرعة   احتفظي بها جيدا
OK.
حسنا
Hurry, hurry!
بسرعة بسرعة
Oh...
هذا هذا هذا
Xingxing.
النجوم
What?
ماذا؟
I also have a gift for you.
لدي أيضا هدية لك
Is that food?
هل هي لذيذة؟
I remember that day
أتذكر ذلك اليوم
you used my belt to fight the enemy.
استخدمت حزامي لمقاومة العدو
You seemed quite adept at it.
يبدو أنك متفوقة للغاية
So I made you this belt
لذا صنعت لك هذا
that can replace weapons.
لحزام الأسلحة
Try it.
جرب
When did you make it?
متى صنعتها؟
Do you like it?
هل أعجبك؟
Yes, I do.
نعم نعم
You've only practiced a few times
لقد تدربت عدة مرات فقط
Are you slacking off?
هل أنت كسول؟
I'm not.
أنا لست كسولًا
Are you all right?
أخي، هل أنت بخير؟
Why do you ask?
لماذا تسأل هكذا
It's you.
أنت
No.
لا
Come here.
تعال بسرعة
I haven't told you yet.
لم أخبرك بعد
Please.
أرجوك
I've already
أنا
let her go.
قد تركتها
Now,
الآن
I'm just fulfilling my old wish.
فقط لتحقيق أمنيتك السابقة
Really?
حقا
Of course.
بالطبع
Silly girl.
يا فتاة سخيفة
Brother, come here.
أخي الأكبر تعال بسرعة
Go.
اذهب
Hurry.
بسرعة
Try this.
تذوق
Delicious.
لذيذ
Really?
حقاً؟
Yes.
نعم
It's all yours.
كلها لك
...two, three.
اثنان ثلاثة
Are you OK?
هل أنت بخير
I'm fine.
أنا بخير
Come on. Have a rest.
تعال واسترح قليلا
OK.
حسنا
Great!
رائع
He finally realized the reality
أخيرًا أدرك الحقيقة
and let go of Xingchen.
وترك النجوم
Otherwise, he would still follow us,
وإلا ما زال يتبعنا
watching Xingchen and Jiang Buting
شاهد النجوم وجيانغ بو دينغ طوال الطريق
That would have been so painful.
سيكون هذا مؤلمًا جدًا
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل
Brother.
أخي
You shouldn't write your romance novel
روايتك الرياح والقمر
so blatantly.
لا يجب أن تكتب بشكل واضح
What are you writing about them every day?
ماذا تكتب كل يوم مع أخي؟
Stop watching.
ما زلت تقرأ
Fine, I won't watch.
حسنًا حسنًا لن أنظر
Xingxing, it's time to take medicine.
النجوم حان وقت تناول الدواء
OK.
حسناً
You should eat this today.
يجب أن نأكل هذا اليوم
Open your mouth.
هيا
Why are the colors different every day?
لماذا لون الطعام مختلف كل يوم؟
There are white, pink, purple, yellow.
‫يوجد أبيض وردي وردي‬
It's green today.
اليوم نأكل اللون الأخضر
Maybe my master
ربما معلمي
has a girlish heart.
لديه قلب فتاة
How are you feeling?
كيف حالك
Are you feeling unwell?
هل أنت بخير؟
Xingchen, what's wrong?
النجوم، ما الخطب؟
Nothing.
لا شيء
Xing...
شينج
Why are you staring at me?
لماذا تنظر إلي؟
Why are you laughing?
لماذا تضحك؟
What's wrong with you?
لا ما بك
Little cutie.
‫محبوبة‬
Little cutie?
محبوبة
Oh.
أوه
You are so cute!
لماذا أنت لطيفة جدا
You're so cute!
‫لطيفة جداً‬
Ah.
يا
Why are you so cute?
لماذا أنت لطيف جدا
No.
لا
No, no, no. Let go of me.
لا لا لا اتركني
What's wrong with her?
ما خطب النجوم؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف
Ugly thing.
قبيح
You are ugly thing!
شيء قبيح
They are so ugly.
قبيح جدا
Xingchen.
النجوم
Horse.
حصان
Yes.
نعم
A horse can speak?
أخي
Hey.
!مهلاً
This horse can speak!
هذا الحصان يستطيع التحدث
This is Transmutation Pill's side effect.
!هذا هو آثار حبوب الكيمياء
Please forgive us.
رجاءً سامحني
Ugly thing, why are you looking at me?
أيها القبيح لماذا تنظر إلي
Who are you calling ugly thing?
من هو قبيح؟
Hey.
مهلاً.
Ugly thing, why are you so mean?
أيها القبيح، لماذا أنت عنيف؟
Brother.
يا أخي
You think you're right for being ugly?
أنت قبيح أنت معقول
Let's go.
هيا بنا
Why are you calling me ugly thing?
لماذا توبخني بشعة
Ugly thing.
قبيح
Let's go.
هيا بنا
You're just an ugly thing,
أنت قبيح
both ugly and dark-skinned.
قبيح وسود
I finally understand
لقد فهمت
Her aesthetic sense is badly distorted now.
إن جمال النجوم مشوهة للغاية الآن
I think the effect of that medicine
أعتقد أن قوة الدواء
has reached her brain.
قد وصلت إلى عقلها
She's like a six-year-old girl now.
إنها الآن مثل فتاة ست سنوات
But she can't call me ugly thing.
لا يمكنها أن توبخني بشعة
She even called me ugly thing.
لقد وبختني بشعة
Only you two are ugly.
أنتما فقط قبيحان
I am...
أنا
horse.
‫حصان‬
Why didn't she call my brother ugly thing?
لماذا أخي ليس قبيحا
They look like pig ears.
مثل أذن الخنزير
Really?
حقاً؟
Xingchen seems to have gotten worse.
ماذا يجب أن نفعل؟ يبدو أن النجوم أكثر خطورة
Who is the Xingchen?
من النجوم؟
Brother, what are we doing here?
أخي، لماذا نحن هنا؟
My master's scrolls say that the fog in the
لقد قرأت في كتاب معلمي
Sophora Town Forbidden Zone can stabilize
الضباب الغامض في المنطقة المحظورة
one's mind, which should help Xingchen.
يجب أن يساعد النجوم
Let's go in and have a look.
هيا لندخل ونلقي نظرة
Hey, brother.
أخي
Why is this road
لا
so eerie?
لماذا هذا الطريق مظلم
Is the Forbidden Zone here?
هل المكان المحرم هنا؟
Logically speaking,
من المنطقي
it's so foggy here.
الضباب هنا ثقيل جدا
The Forbidden Zone should not be far.
يجب أن يكون المكان المحرم قريبًا
Take a look at the map.
انظر الخريطة
Why is it so frightening here?
مخيف جدا ماذا
Where are we?
أين نحن؟
Buting.
بودينغ
Look what I've brought you?
انظر ماذا أحضرت لك
Don't shout.
لا تصرخ
No.
لا
So adorable like this.
كم هذا لطيف
Look at them.
انظر إليهم
They like you so much.
يحبونك كثيرا
Let's go and say hello.
هيا، لنذهب ونلقي التحية
Stop.
توقف
What have you brought?
ما الذي أحضرته؟
Go back now.
ارجع بسرعة
Let go of your hands.
اترك يدك
Xingchen is holding a monster.
المشكلة أن النجوم تمسك غريبًا
Xingchen, danger, danger, danger!
النجوم، إنها خطيرة
Let the monster disappear!
!اجعل الوحوش تختفي
Shut up.
ماذا؟
Don't scare them.
لا
They all like you very much.
جميعهم يحبونك
See?
هل رأيت؟
He's greeting you.
أنا ألقي التحية عليك
Come on.
بسرعة
Stop.
توقف
L-L-Let go!
اتركني
Monster!
وحش
Danger, danger, danger!
‫خطير خطير خطير‬
It's OK. Don't be afraid.
لا بأس لا تخافي
Back off!
تراجعوا تراجعوا
Xingxing! Xingxing!
النجوم النجوم النجوم
I saw him. He's cute.
لقد رأيت، إنه لطيف جدًا
You come here first.
تعال أولا
Let's play with him later, OK?
دعنا نلعب معه بعد قليل
Why don't you shake hands first?
امسك بيدك أولا
No, no. You come here first.
لا لا تعال أولا
Later,
بعد قليل
we will play with him later, OK?
نلعب معه بعد قليل
Come here.
تعال أولا
Hurry up. Come here.
تعال
We will play with him later.
لنلعب معه بعد قليل
Come.
هيا
Stand still.
قف
So cute.
لطيف جدا
Come on.
تعال بسرعة
Oh.
يا إلهي
Cutie.
محبوبة
All right, all right.
حسنا حسنا
Let him come back.
دعه يعود
You little brat! Come back here.
أيها الأحمق، عد
Let's fight.
لنتقاتل
Oh my god!
‫يا إلهي‬
Oh my goodness, it's so scary!
‫يا إلهي لقد أخفتني‬
My cutie is gone.
‫يا حبيبتي الصغيرة قد رحلت‬
It's OK.
لا بأس
Xingchen, are you OK?
النجوم، هل أنت بخير؟
It's gone. Forget it.
حسنًا، لقد اختفت
This Sophora Town
هذه بلدة جوى
is indeed strange.
غريب بعض الشيء
Everyone, follow closely.
اتبعوا الجميع
Don't get separated.
لا تفرقوا
OK.
نعم
There seems to be a house ahead.
يبدو أن هناك شخص في الأمام
Let's find out where the Forbidden Zone is.
دعنا نسأل أين المنطقة المحظورة
Brother, hold on to Xingchen.
أيها الأخ الأكبر، خذ النجوم
Hurry up!
هيا
Oh god.
حقا
Don't be afraid.
لا تخافي
Yes.
نعم
Little cutie, don't run.
لا تهرب يا عزيزتي
Hey, Xingchen.
النجوم
Xingxing, where are you going?
أين ستذهبين؟
It's OK. I'll get her back.
لا بأس سأسحبها
No one is here.
لا يوجد أحد هنا
It's so strange.
هذا غريب
The lanterns are still on.
المصباح لا يزال مفتوحًا
But why is no one answering?
لماذا لم يرد أحد
Brother.
أخي
How about I go inside and take a look?
هل يجب أن أجد طريقة للدخول؟
That works.
حسنا
But there must be many villagers
لكن في هذه القرية
inside this village.
يجب أن يكون هناك الكثير من القرويين
Keep your voice down. Don't disturb them.
أخفض صوتك لا تزعجهم
Don't worry.
لا تقلق
Hey.
مهلاً
Let's go inside.
ادخل
Xingxing. Brother.
‫النجوم الأخ الأكبر
Let's go.
لنذهب
Coming.
أنا قادم
This table is clean.
هذه الطاولة نظيفة
Someone was embroidering here just now.
هناك شخص يطرز الزهور هنا للتو
What's that smell?
ما هذه الرائحة؟
Wow.
‫واو‬
Smells good. It's braised pork!
رائحته شهية، لحم الخنزير المطهو ببطء
Xingchen, this is noodles.
النجوم هذه المعكرونة
No. Stop it.
لا
You...
ماذا تفعل؟
Horse.
الحصان
This place
هذا المكان
feels like
مثل في الظلام
there are countless unseen eyes
هناك العديد من العيون التي لا يمكنك رؤيتها
watching you from the shadows.
يراقبك
There were so many people just now.
كان هناك الكثير من الناس
The moment we came in,
في لحظة دخلنا
it became a ghost town
تحولنا إلى مدينة ميتة
with no sign of anyone
لا يوجد أي شخص
Brother.
أخي الكبير
Don't be afraid.
لا تخف
I'm here.
أنا هنا
I'm not afraid.
لا أخاف
You're the one who's shaking.
أنت من سحبتني
Don't panic.
لا داعي للذعر
Look.
انظروا
The fire in the stove hasn't extinguished.
لم يتم إطفاء النار في الموقد
The noodles in the pot are not soggy.
‫لم يتم إطفاء المعكرونة في الوعاء‬
The candles outside
الشموع في الخارج
are still burning.
لا تزال تحترق
Here.
هنا
There must be someone just now.
يجب أن يكون هناك شخص
Mom!
أمي
What's wrong?
ماذا حدث
Let's see if dad's noodles are ready.
لنذهب لنرى إذا كان المعكرونة جاهزة أم لا
Yes.
نعم
It's ready.
انتهيت
You're sweating.
انظر إلى عرقك
It's OK.
لا بأس لا بأس
We can have dinner soon.
يمكننا تناول الطعام بعد قليل
Mom.
أمي
There must have been residents here,
يجب أن يكون هناك سكان هنا
they've just temporarily hidden.
اختبئ مؤقتًا
How about this?
هكذا
Let's split up.
سنقسم الفريق
and search separately.
لنبحث بشكل منفصل
Find the Forbidden Zone as soon as possible.
ابحثوا عن المنطقة المحظورة في أقرب وقت ممكن
OK. OK.
حسنا حسنا
OK.
جيد
Cutie, didn't you say
يا صغيرتي
you'd take me to catch butterflies?
ألم تقل أنك ستأخذني للقبض على الفراشة؟
Yes.
نعم
I want to take you to catch butterflies.
أريد أن آخذك للقبض على الفراشة
But we...
لكننا
we're going there to catch butterflies.
سنذهب إلى هناك للقبض على الفراشة
You must follow me closely.
يجب أن تتبعني
The fog over there seems to be thicker.
يبدو أن الضباب هناك قوي قليلاً
Hey...
هذا
Xingxing!
النجوم
Huo Xingchen!
"هيو شينغ تشين"
Little cutie!
‫محبوبة‬
Xingchen!
النجوم
Little cutie, slow down!
عزيزتي، ركضي ببطء
Cutie.
‫يا صغيرتي‬
Oh no.
لا
Brother.
أخي
Are you scared?
هل أنت خائف؟
No.
لا أخاف
I have no right to be afraid.scared
ليس لدي الحق للخوف
I must protect you.
لحماية أخي الأكبر
Alright.
حسناً
Brother.
أخي
With your words,
لا أخاف
Actually, I'm still afraid.
في الواقع ما زلت خائفة
My legs aren't listening to me anymore.
ساقي لا تستمع إلي
A-A-Aren't you brave?
ألست شجاعة
What honest child wouldn't be afraid?
من لا يخاف الطفل الصادق
My god!
يا إلهي
Brother,
أخي الكبير، أخبرني
are we really unlucky?
لن نكون محظوظين هكذا
Have we actually met...
لقد التقينا حقاً
No, no.
لا لا
No.
لا يمكن
Little cutie.
‫يا صغيرتي‬
Little cutie, slow down.
‫يا صغيرتي اركضي ببطء‬
Little cutie!
محبوبة
Xingchen!
النجوم
Xingchen, watch out!
النجوم خطيرة
What's your name?
ما اسمك؟
Let me touch you.
دعني ألمسك
Xingchen, come here!
النجوم، تعال بسرعة
Horse?
الحصان
I'll tell you,
دعني أخبرك
even if you are a horse,
حتى لو كنت حصان
I won't give you my little cutie.
‫لن أترك طفلي لك‬
Because I want to give it to Buting.
‫لأنني أريد أن أمسك بودينغ للعب‬
Little cutie.
‫محبوبة‬
Little cutie, don't run!
!عزيزتي، لا تهربي
Xingchen!
النجوم
Little cutie!
‫محبوبة‬
Little cutie.
محبوبة
Xingchen.
النجوم
Little cutie, where have you been?
يا صغيرتي إلى أين ذهبت يا صغيرتي
Why is there so much smoke?
لماذا هذا الدخان الكبير
What's that smell?
ما هذه الرائحة
It smells so good.
رائحته شهية
Xingchen.
النجوم
There's a butterfly.
هناك فراشة
Star, it's OK now.
النجوم، لا بأس
I'll take you home.
سآخذك إلى المنزل
Xingchen.
النجوم